{
    "id": "42f3fd0dde004d78bfc7d8d788c56bf5",
    "title": "Prepositions activity",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "75cfe71cda2448c2aa8c34357aacff9d",
            "title": "Prepositions Quiz",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "The child ran ..................... the road.",
                    "description": "Across means 'on or to the other side of a flat area or surface. ",
                    "answers": [
                        "across",
                        "through",
                        "over"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The river flows ..................... the bridge.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "under",
                        "below",
                        "before"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "The work was done ………………….. haste.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "with",
                        "at",
                        "in"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "He goes ..................... church every Sunday.",
                    "description": "To indicates direction.",
                    "answers": [
                        "for",
                        "in",
                        "to"
                    ],
                    "correct": 2
                },
                {
                    "question": "The thieves jumped ..................... the wall.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "above",
                        "over",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He spoke ..................... me ………………… French.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "for, in",
                        "to, in",
                        "to, with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "The moon does not shine ...................... its own light.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "by",
                        "with"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "I am tired ………………… walking.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "of",
                        "at"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "He has yet to recover ..................... his illness.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "from",
                        "with",
                        "of"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Do not cry …………………. spilt milk.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "over",
                        "for",
                        "on"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}